intuilab.com 2019-03-14

# Privacy Policy | Intuiface

Intuilab SAS (”The Company“) respects its Users’ privacy and is committed to protecting any personal information shared with The Company. This statement describes how The Company uses personal information shared by Users.

###  **Personal Information**

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, such as a first and last name, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, occupation, industry, personal interests, and other information. The Company does not automatically collect personal information, including Users’ email address. The Company does log Users’ IP addresses, but does not link such IP addresses to any personal information unless such was voluntarily provided by Users. The Site may use standard technologies, such as “cookies” and other HTML tools, to collect information about the use of the Site. The Company may collect personal information when such is voluntarily provided by Users (for example: if Users request further information, register to a mailing list, etc.) Also, The Company may receive personal information from business partners and vendors. The Company only uses such information if it has been collected in accordance with acceptable privacy practices consistent with this Privacy Statement and applicable laws. Access to certain The Company web pages requires a login and a password. Unless the User requests deactivation of his or her personal information as specified below, his or her personal information may be retained by The Company to verify compliance with any applicable agreements and understandings, log software licenses granted, track software downloaded from those pages, or track usage of other applications available on those pages.

###  **Notice**

When personal information is collected, The Company will so inform Users and shall also inform the Users of the purpose of the collection. The Company will not transfer Users’ personal information to third parties without their specific consent, except under the limited conditions described under the discussion entitled “Information Sharing and Disclosure” below. The Company provides its Users with the opportunity to “opt in” prior to receiving direct marketing or market research information. In other words, The Company will require its Users’ affirmative action before it may use their information for purposes other than the purpose for which it was submitted. At all times, The Company will always give its Users the opportunity to “opt out” of receiving such materials.

###  **Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

The Company uses common Internet technologies, such as cookies and IP addresses, to keep track of interactions with the Company's website and software.

 **Cookies  **A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to Users’ computer’s hard drive when such Users visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the Site uses to track the pages visited by Users, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information provided by Users. Some parts of the Site use cookies to track user traffic patterns. A User who prefers not to receive cookies while browsing the Site or via HTML-formatted emails can customize his or her browser to warn him or her before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when his or her browser alerts him or her to its presence. A User can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in his or her browser, which refusal may adversely affect the User’s experience.

 **IP Addresses  **When you visit The Company Web sites, or launch Composer and Player, the Company collects your Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses. Doing so enables The Company 1) for the Web: to track and aggregate non-personal information, 2) for Composer/Player: to check license status and product stability. For example, The Company uses IP addresses to monitor the regions from which Customers and Visitors navigate the Company’s websites.

 **Remarketing Codes  **We use Google remarketing codes and cookies to log when users view specific pages or take specific actions on our website. This enables us to provide targeted advertising in the future via ads that will appear on 3rd party websites. If you would like to opt out of our targeted ad activities, visit the Google  **[Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads)**  page.

###  **Intuiface**

With the Free Edition of Composer, the .ifx file - i.e. the XML-based text file used by Intuiface to store the structure of an experience - is uploaded onto The Company servers from time to time for internal use only, enabling investigation of usage statistics and product enhancement. Intuiface never uploads media (such as videos, images, docs, etc.) referenced by the uploaded .ifx file.

For all Composer plans, the .ifx file and related media are uploaded onto The Company servers when publishing an experience to Intuiface Cloud Storage. The Company never uses this data. In addition, the .ifx file will be uploaded when the user grants Composer permission to send a crash report to The Company as an aid in troubleshooting. The .ifx file will only be used for troubleshooting analysis.

With the API Explorer feature of Intuiface Composer, API requests (domain name, endpoint, parameter names and values) entered by a user, who is logged in under an Intuiface account, are stored on The Company servers as that account’s API request history in order to be reused later on by – and exclusively for - the same Intuiface account. Changes made by the user to the API request’s results - both property selection and property type categorization - are also stored to continuously train the API Explorer’s machine learning algorithms.

With Intuiface Analytics, an Intuiface Composer user may choose to activate the Data Tracking feature to capture and send designated data collected from one Experience on one or more devices to an The Company database server in the cloud that processes this collected data. It is the full and unique responsibility of the Intuiface Composer user to capture and use data resulting in accordance with the laws of the countries where this Intuiface Experience is played. The Company never uses this data. The Licensee (as defined in the [Intuiface License Agreement](https://support.intuiface.com/hc/en-us/articles/360007434631-Intuiface-License-Agreement)) is the owner of the collected data.

###  **IntuiPad**

The Intuiface remote control - the IntuiPad - is network-capable:

The Internet Client capability establishes outbound access to the Internet and public networks through a firewall. The private Network Client Server capability establishes inbound and outbound access to home and work networks through a firewall. Through use of the above two capabilities, IntuiPad can auto-detect running Intuiface experiences on network-accessible PCs, identifying and locally saving their associated Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses.

###  **How The Company May Use Information Collected**

The Company uses information for several general purposes: to fulfill Users’ requests for certain products and services, to personalize Users’ experience on the Site, to maintain ongoing contacts with its Users, to improve its products using crash report information, and to better understand its Users’ needs and provide them with better services. The Company may also use Users’ information to send them, using internal or third-party platforms, direct marketing information or contact them for market research.

###  **Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Users’ personal information is never shared with third parties without the Users’ permission, except under any of the following circumstances:

When a User has expressed his or her consent to share such information; If sharing such information is necessary to provide a product or service requested by a User (in which case, The Company will only provide to such third parties the information they need to deliver the service. Also, such companies are prohibited from using Users’ information for any other purpose); As part of a joint sales promotion or to pass sales leads to one of The Company’s distribution partners; and The Company may also disclose Users’ personal information if required to do so by law, to enforce The Company’s Terms of Use, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or the Site.

###  **Deactivation of User Information**

A User may request deactivation of his or her account or any of his or her personal information held by us by sending an email to info [at] The Company [dot] com. If a User chooses to deactivate his or her account, The Company may retain in its files some personal information to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, enforce its Terms of Use, and comply with legal requirements as permitted by law.

###  **Data Security**

Users’ account information is password-protected. The Company shall safeguard the security of data provided by Users with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. In certain areas of our websites, The Company uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to enhance the security of sensitive data transmissions. However, The Company cannot ensure the complete security of the information transmitted by Users.

###  **Third Party Sites**

The Company’s website contains links to other sites. The Company does not share its Users’ personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices.

###  **Changes to this Privacy Statement**

The Company may amend this privacy statement from time to time. In case any substantial changes are made to this Privacy Statement, The Company will make that information known to its Users by posting a notice on the Site.

###  **Questions or Suggestions**

Any questions or concerns about The Company’s privacy policy may be e-mailed to **privacy @ intuiface.com**.
